Office of Educational Affairs, School of Medicine Records UA146
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office of Educational Affairs, School of Medicine Records
1968 -- 2019
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office for Educational Affairs
Lee, Mary Y.
Dean for Educational Affairs
UA146
51.6 Linear Feet 43 record cartons
22 Digital Object(s)
4.37 Gigabytes Of the 22 digital objects in this collection, 13 have extent information and comprise 4.37 GBs of data.
This collection contains records created by the Office of Educational Affairs in the School of Medicine.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by the Office of Educational Affairs of the School of Medicine, 2007-2018.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into four series: School of Medicine Syllabi; Unprocessed accessions; School of Medicine class schedules and committee minutes; and Mary Y. Lee's files.
Biographical / Historical
Beginning with the creation of a Committee on Instruction, a move to compartmentalize the internal administration of the School of Medicine, this department would later become the Medical Education Group, or "Blue Sky" Committee, the Task Force on Curriculum Planning, the Curriculum Committee, and then finally, the Office of Educational Affairs. As of 2017, the head of this office is the Dean for Educational Affairs at the School of Medicine, and the office is responsible for overseeing all administrative work related to curriculum, educational grants, faculty support, and class scheduling, as well as managing the Clinical Skills and Simulation Center (CSSC).
In 1913, the School of Medicine had grown sufficiently in numbers and complexity to require a reorganization of its internal administration. The school was split into six departments and the needs of these departments were represented by a Committee on Instruction. The creation of the Committee on Instruction relieved the Administrative Committee of much of the burden of settling purely educational matters and allowed it to concentrate on the business affairs of the school and the activities which required review or action by the Tufts Trustees. The Committee on Instruction met monthly.
In 1968, the Medical Education Group (also known as the Faculty "Blue Sky" Committee) submitted a proposal for curricular reform titled the "Blue Sky Report." The "Blue Sky" group met regularly to create a new formulation of the goals and structures of the curriculum and became the Task Force on Curriculum Planning. They would later become the Curriculum Committee. As a result of the "Blue Sky Report," the Office of Educational Affairs, at the time called the Office of Research in Educational and Organizational Innovation, began to structuralize.
As of 2017, the OEA is located at 145 Harrison Avenue, Boston, MA. The Dean for Educational Affairs at the School of Medicine is Scott K. Epstein, MD. The office is responsible for overseeing curricular development, managing educational grants, supporting the teaching faculty, providing administrative support, and scheduling space for classes, conferences, and meetings in the Health Sciences campus. It also manages the Clinical Skills and Simulation Center (CSSC), a training facility for clinical skills and diagnostic reasoning practice on computerized mannequins.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains Tufts School of Medicine course syllabi, class schedules, committee minutes, and subject files. The subject files were compiled by Mary Y. Lee, former Dean of Education Affairs at the School of Medicine. They include agendas, minutes, annual reports, correspondence, and grant applications.
Curriculum and Instruction -- Teaching Material; Curriculum and Instruction -- Faculty; Teaching and learning
- School of Medicine Syllabi, 1985 -- 2020; 1989 -- 2014; UA146.001; 36.0 Linear Feet; 18 Digital Object(s) 18 digital objects containing 192 files.; 3.33 Gigabytes Of the 18 digital objects in this series, 13 have extent information and comprise 4.37 GBs of data.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains syllabi for courses offered by the Tufts School of Medicine. The syllabi are received from and managed by the Office of Educational Affairs. File titles in this series are comprised of the course name, the School of Medicine class year, and the type of course by year in the program (i.e. first year, second year, etc.) The academic year during which the course was offered can be deduced from this information.
  Arrangement
  This series is not arranged.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Addiction Medicine Syllabus, 2007, Second Year, UA146.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Biochemistry Conferences, 2009, First Year, UA146.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Biochemistry Conferences, 2010, First Year, UA146.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Cardiovascular Pathophysiology Syllabus, 2007, Second Year, UA146.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Cardiovascular Systemic Pathology, 2007, Second Year, UA146.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Cardiovascular Systemic Pathology, 2007, Second Year, UA146.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Endocrine Systemic Pathology, 2006, Second Year, UA146.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Evidence Based Medicine Syllabus, 2008, Second Year, UA146.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Gastrointestinal Systemic Pathology, 2006, Second Year, UA146.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Gastrointestinal Systemic Pathology, 2007, Second Year, UA146.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Infectious Diseases Pathophysiology Syllabus, 2006, Second Year, UA146.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Medical Physiology Syllabus - Volume II, 2008, First Year, UA146.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Microbiology Syllabus, 2009, Second Year, UA146.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Musculoskeletal Systemic Pathology Syllabus, 2007, Second Year, UA146.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Musculoskeletal Systemic Pathology Syllabus, 2008, Second Year, UA146.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Nutrition and Medicine Syllabus, 2008, First Year, UA146.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Part I of V, 2008, Second Year, UA146.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Part III of V, 2007, Second Year, UA146.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Population Medicine Syllabus Part 1, 2007, Second Year, UA146.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Population Medicine Syllabus Part 2, 2006, Second Year, UA146.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - Population Medicine Syllabus Part II, 2007, Second Year, UA146.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Psychopathology Handbook for Conference Leaders, 2004, Second Year, UA146.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Psychopathology Syllabus, 2003, Second Year, UA146.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - Psychopathology Syllabus, 2004, Second Year, UA146.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - Psychopathology Syllabus, 2005, Second Year, UA146.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
  - Psychopathology Syllabus, 2006, Second Year, UA146.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - Psychopathology Syllabus, 2006, Second Year, UA146.001.001.00027 (Box 1)
  - Psychopathology Syllabus, 2008, Second Year, UA146.001.001.00028 (Box 1)
  - Psychopathology Syllabus,, Second Year, UA146.001.001.00029 (Box 1)
  - Pulmonary System Schedule (no Cover),, Second year, UA146.001.001.00030 (Box 1)
  - Pulmonary Systemic Pathology Syllabus, 2005, Second Year, UA146.001.001.00031 (Box 1)
  - Pulmonary Systemic Pathology Syllabus, 2006, Second Year, UA146.001.001.00032 (Box 1)
  - Pulmonary Systemic Pathology Syllabus, 2007, Second Year, UA146.001.001.00033 (Box 1)
  - Reproductive Systemic Pathology Syllabus, 2005, Second Year, UA146.001.001.00034 (Box 1)
  - The Breast and Pelvic Examination Syllabus, 1998, UA146.001.001.00035 (Box 1)
  - Interviewing and the Doctor/Patient relationship Syllabus, 2005, First Year, UA146.001.001.00036 (Box 1)
  - Molecular Biology Syllabus, 2006, First Year, UA146.001.001.00037 (Box 1)
  - Molecular Biology Syllabus, 2007, First Year, UA146.001.001.00038 (Box 1)
  - Cell, Tissue, and Organ Biology Syllabus, 2009, First Year, UA146.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Endocrine Systemic Pathology, 2006, Second Year, UA146.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Epidemiology/Biostatistics Syllabus, 2006, First Year, UA146.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - General Pathology Syllabus, 2006, Second Year, UA146.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - General Pathology Syllabus, 2009, First Year, UA146.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Medical Clinical Anatomy Syllabus, 2009, First Year, UA146.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Medical Physiology Syllabus- Volume II, 2009, First Year, UA146.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Musculoskeletal System Pathology Syllabus, 2003, Second Year, UA146.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Musculoskeletal System Syllabus, UA146.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Part II of V, 2007, Second Year, UA146.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Part III of V, 2007, Second Year, UA146.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Part IV of V, 2006, Second Year, UA146.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Part IV of V, 2007, Second Year, UA146.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Part V of V, 2006, Second Year, UA146.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Part V of V, 2007, Second Year, UA146.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - Physical Diagnosis I; Clinical Skills Syllabus, 2009, First Year, UA146.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - Physical Diagnosis II Syllabus, 2007, Second Year, UA146.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - Physical Diagnosis II Syllabus, 2008, Second Year, UA146.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - Population Medicine Syllabus Part 1, 2006, Second Year, UA146.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - Psychopathology Syllabus, 2003, Second Year, UA146.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
  - Reproductive Pathophysiology Syllabus, 2006, Second Year, UA146.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
  - Systemic Pathology Musculoskeletal Syllabus, 2004, Second Year, UA146.001.002.00022 (Box 2)
  - Systemic Pathology Musculoskeletal Syllabus, 2005, Second Year, UA146.001.002.00023 (Box 2)
  - Systemic Pathology Musculoskeletal Syllabus, 2005, Second Year, UA146.001.002.00024 (Box 2)
  - Systemic Pathology Musculoskeletal Syllabus, 2006, Second Year, UA146.001.002.00025 (Box 2)
  - Systemic Pathology Renal Syllabus, 2005, Second Year, UA146.001.002.00026 (Box 2)
  - Addiction Medicine Syllabus, 2004, Second Year, UA146.001.002.00027 (Box 2)
  - Cardiovascular Pathophysiology Syllabus, 2007, Second Year, UA146.001.002.00028 (Box 2)
  - Cardiovascular Systemic Pathology Syllabus, 2007, Second Year, UA146.001.002.00029 (Box 2)
  - General Pathology Syllabus, 2007, Second Year, UA146.001.002.00030 (Box 2)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Part IV of V, 2008, Second Year, UA146.001.002.00031 (Box 2)
  - Physical Diagnosis II Syllabus, 2006, UA146.001.002.00032 (Box 2)
  - Addiction Medicine Syllabus, 2006, Second Year, UA146.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Addiction Medicine Syllabus, 2008, Second Year, UA146.001.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - Biochemistry Syllabus, 2006, First Year, UA146.001.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - Endocrine Pathophysiology Syllabus, 2006, Second Year, UA146.001.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - Epidemiology/Biostatistics Syllabus, 2005, First Year, UA146.001.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - Gastrointestinal Pathophysiology Syllabus, 2006, Second Year, UA146.001.003.00006 (Box 3)
  - Immunology Syllabus, 2009, First Year, UA146.001.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - Interviewing and the Doctor/Patient relationship Syllabus, 2006, First Year, UA146.001.003.00008 (Box 3)
  - Microbiology Lab Syllabus, 2004, Second Year, UA146.001.003.00009 (Box 3)
  - Microbiology Syllabus, 2004, Second Year, UA146.001.003.00010 (Box 3)
  - Molecular Biology Syllabus, 2005, First Year, UA146.001.003.00011 (Box 3)
  - Musculoskeletal Pathophysiology Syllabus, 2004, Second Year, UA146.001.003.00012 (Box 3)
  - Neuroscience Lab Manual, 2007, Second Year, UA146.001.003.00013 (Box 3)
  - Neuroscience Syllabus, 2006, Second Year, UA146.001.003.00014 (Box 3)
  - Pathophysiology Musculoskeletal Syllabus, 2005, Second Year, UA146.001.003.00015 (Box 3)
  - Patient/Doctor/Society Syllabus, 2004, First Year, UA146.001.003.00016 (Box 3)
  - Patient/Doctor/Society Syllabus Part III of IV, 2004, First Year, UA146.001.003.00017 (Box 3)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Part V of V, 2007, Second Year, UA146.001.003.00018 (Box 3)
  - Physical Diagnosis II Syllabus, 2009, Second Year, UA146.001.003.00019 (Box 3)
  - Population Medicine Syllabus Part 1, 2006, Second Year, UA146.001.003.00020 (Box 3)
  - Psychopathology Handbook for Conference Leaders, 2003, Second Year, UA146.001.003.00021 (Box 3)
  - Renal Pathophysiology Syllabus, 2006, Second Year, UA146.001.003.00022 (Box 3)
  - Renal Pathophysiology Syllabus, 2007, Second Year, UA146.001.003.00023 (Box 3)
  - Endocrine Pathophysiology Syllabus, 2006, Second Year, UA146.001.003.00024 (Box 3)
  - Endocrine Pathophysiology Syllabus, 2007, Second Year, UA146.001.003.00025 (Box 3)
  - Interviewing and the Doctor/Patient relationship Syllabus, 2008, First Year, UA146.001.003.00026 (Box 3)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Part II, A of V, 2008, Second Year, UA146.001.003.00027 (Box 3)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Part II, B of V, 2008, Second Year, UA146.001.003.00028 (Box 3)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Part III of V, 2008, Second Year, UA146.001.003.00029 (Box 3)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Part III of V, 2008, Second Year, UA146.001.003.00030 (Box 3)
  - Renal Systemic Pathology Syllabus, 2007, Second Year, UA146.001.003.00031 (Box 3)
  - Reproductive Pathophysiology Syllabus, 2007, Second Year, UA146.001.003.00032 (Box 3)
  - Cardiovascular Pathophysiology Syllabus, 2006, Second Year, UA146.001.004.00001 (Box 4)
  - Medical Genetics Syllabus, 2005, Second Year, UA146.001.004.00002 (Box 4)
  - Medical Genetics Syllabus, 2006, Second Year, UA146.001.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - Medical Genetics Syllabus, 2007, Second Year, UA146.001.004.00004 (Box 4)
  - Medical Microbiology Laboratory, 2006, UA146.001.004.00005 (Box 4)
  - Medical Microbiology Laboratory, 2009, UA146.001.004.00006 (Box 4)
  - Microbiology Syllabus, 2007, Second Year, UA146.001.004.00007 (Box 4)
  - Neuroscience Syllabus, 2009, Second Year, UA146.001.004.00008 (Box 4)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Part I of V, 2006, Second Year, UA146.001.004.00009 (Box 4)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Part II of V, 2006, Second Year, UA146.001.004.00010 (Box 4)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Part V of V, 2008, Second Year, UA146.001.004.00011 (Box 4)
  - Physical Diagnosis II Syllabus, 2009, Second Year, UA146.001.004.00012 (Box 4)
  - Physical Diagnosis II Syllabus, 2009, Second Year, UA146.001.004.00013 (Box 4)
  - Physical Diagnosis II Syllabus, 2009, Second Year, UA146.001.004.00014 (Box 4)
  - Population Medicine Syllabus Part I, 2008, Second Year, UA146.001.004.00015 (Box 4)
  - Pulmonary Pathophysiology Slide Syllabus, 2006, Second Year, UA146.001.004.00016 (Box 4)
  - Pulmonary Pathophysiology Syllabus, 2006, Second Year, UA146.001.004.00017 (Box 4)
  - Renal System Course Syllabus, 2002, UA146.001.004.00018 (Box 4)
  - Renal Systemic Pathology Syllabus, 2006, Second Year, UA146.001.004.00019 (Box 4)
  - Renal Systemic Pathology Syllabus, 2009, Second year, UA146.001.004.00020 (Box 4)
  - Reproductive System Pathology, 2004, UA146.001.004.00021 (Box 4)
  - Reproductive Systemic Pathology Syllabus, 2006, Second Year, UA146.001.004.00022 (Box 4)
  - Gastrointestinal Pathophysiology Syllabus, 2006, Second year, UA146.001.004.00023 (Box 4)
  - Neuroscience Syllabus, 2007, Second Year, UA146.001.004.00024 (Box 4)
  - Nutrition and Medicine Syllabus, 2009, First Year, UA146.001.004.00025 (Box 4)
  - Pathophysiology Musculoskeletal Syllabus, 2005, Second Year, UA146.001.004.00026 (Box 4)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Part I of V, 2008, Second Year, UA146.001.004.00027 (Box 4)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus part II of V, 2007, Second Year, UA146.001.004.00028 (Box 4)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Part II, B of V, 2008, Second Year, UA146.001.004.00029 (Box 4)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Part III of V, 2006, Second Year, UA146.001.004.00030 (Box 4)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Part V of V, 2008, Second Year, UA146.001.004.00031 (Box 4)
  - Population Medicine Syllabus Part I, 2009, Second Year, UA146.001.004.00032 (Box 4)
  - Gastrointestinal Pathophysiology Syllabus, 2007, Second year, UA146.001.005.00001 (Box 5)
  - Infectious Diseases Pathophysiology Syllabus, 2007, Second Year, UA146.001.005.00002 (Box 5)
  - Musculoskeletal Pathophysiology Syllabus, 2006, Second Year, UA146.001.005.00003 (Box 5)
  - Musculoskeletal Pathophysiology Syllabus, 2007, Second Year, UA146.001.005.00004 (Box 5)
  - Neuroscience Lab Manuel, 2007, Second Year, UA146.001.005.00005 (Box 5)
  - Neuroscience Syllabus,, Second Year, UA146.001.005.00006 (Box 5)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Part I of V, 2008, Second Year, UA146.001.005.00007 (Box 5)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Part II, A of V, 2008, Second Year, UA146.001.005.00008 (Box 5)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Part II, B of V, 2008, Second Year, UA146.001.005.00009 (Box 5)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Part III of V, 2008, Second Year, UA146.001.005.00010 (Box 5)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Part IV of V, 2008, Second Year, UA146.001.005.00011 (Box 5)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Part IV of V, 2008, Second Year, UA146.001.005.00012 (Box 5)
  - Reproductive Systemic Pathology Syllabus, 2006, Second Year, UA146.001.005.00013 (Box 5)
  - Reproductive Systemic Pathology Syllabus, 2007, Second Year, UA146.001.005.00014 (Box 5)
  - Cell, Tissue, and Organ Biology Syllabus Part II, 2001, First Year, UA146.001.005.00015 (Box 5)
  - Endocrine System Pathology Syllabus, 2002, UA146.001.005.00016 (Box 5)
  - Immunology Syllabus, 2001, First Year, UA146.001.005.00017 (Box 5)
  - Immunology Syllabus, 2008, First Year, UA146.001.005.00018 (Box 5)
  - Infectious Diseases Pathophysiology Syllabus, 2005, Second Year, UA146.001.005.00019 (Box 5)
  - Medical Physiology Syllabus - Volume I, 2008, First Year, UA146.001.005.00020 (Box 5)
  - Medical Physiology Syllabus Part I, 2001, UA146.001.005.00021 (Box 5)
  - Microbiology Syllabus, 2006, Second Year, UA146.001.005.00022 (Box 5)
  - Molecular Biology Syllabus, 2001, First Year, UA146.001.005.00023 (Box 5)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Part I of V, 2007, Second Year, UA146.001.005.00024 (Box 5)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Part II A of V, 2008, Second Year, UA146.001.005.00025 (Box 5)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Part II B of V, 2008, Second Year, UA146.001.005.00026 (Box 5)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Part III of V, 2008, Second Year, UA146.001.005.00027 (Box 5)
  - Physical Diagnosis I Part I Syllabus, 2008, First Year, UA146.001.005.00028 (Box 5)
  - Preclinical Selective Program Catalog, 1997, UA146.001.005.00029 (Box 5)
  - Principles and Practice of Medicine, 2001, UA146.001.005.00030 (Box 5)
  - Biochemistry Syllabus, 2001, First Year, UA146.001.006.00001 (Box 6)
  - Cell. Tissue, and Organ Biology Syllabus Part I, 2001, First Year, UA146.001.006.00002 (Box 6)
  - Class of 2001 First Year Fall Semester 1997, 1997, First Year, UA146.001.006.00003 (Box 6)
  - Class of 2001 First Year Spring Semester 1998, 1998, First Year, UA146.001.006.00004 (Box 6)
  - Epidemiology/Biostatistics Syllabus, 2001, First Year, UA146.001.006.00005 (Box 6)
  - Gross Anatomy Abdomen Syllabus, 2001, UA146.001.006.00006 (Box 6)
  - Medical Genetics Syllabus, 2001, UA146.001.006.00007 (Box 6)
  - Medical Gross Anatomy Extremities Syllabus, 2001, UA146.001.006.00008 (Box 6)
  - Medical gross Anatomy Pelvis/Perineum Syllabus, 2000, UA146.001.006.00009 (Box 6)
  - Pathophysiology Endocrine Syllabus, 2002, Second Year, UA146.001.006.00010 (Box 6)
  - Physical Diagnosis I, 2004, First Year, UA146.001.006.00011 (Box 6)
  - Principles and Practice of Medicine I, 2001, UA146.001.006.00012 (Box 6)
  - Principles and Practice of Medicine Patient Doctor Society, 2001, UA146.001.006.00013 (Box 6)
  - Problem Based Learning, 2001, UA146.001.006.00014 (Box 6)
  - Behavioral Science and Primary Care, 1999, UA146.001.006.00015 (Box 6)
  - Biochemistry Conferences Syllabus, 2004, First Year, UA146.001.006.00016 (Box 6)
  - Biochemistry Syllabus, 2004, First Year, UA146.001.006.00017 (Box 6)
  - Cell, Tissue, and Organ Biology Syllabus Part I, 2004, First Year, UA146.001.006.00018 (Box 6)
  - Epidemiology/Biostatistics Syllabus, 1995, First Year, UA146.001.006.00019 (Box 6)
  - Epidemiology/Biostatistics Syllabus, 2004, First Year, UA146.001.006.00020 (Box 6)
  - General Pathology Syllabus, 1998, UA146.001.006.00021 (Box 6)
  - General Pathology Syllabus, 2003, UA146.001.006.00022 (Box 6)
  - Immunology Syllabus, 1995, First Year, UA146.001.006.00023 (Box 6)
  - Immunology Syllabus, 2004, First Year, UA146.001.006.00024 (Box 6)
  - Infectious Diseases Syllabus, 1998, UA146.001.006.00025 (Box 6)
  - Microbiology Lab Syllabus, 2003, Second Year, UA146.001.006.00026 (Box 6)
  - Microbiology Syllabus, 2003, Second Year, UA146.001.006.00027 (Box 6)
  - Neuroscience Lab Manuel, 2003, Second Year, UA146.001.006.00028 (Box 6)
  - Neuroscience Syllabus, 2003, Second Year, UA146.001.006.00029 (Box 6)
  - Perspectives in Clinical Medicine, 2003, Second Year, UA146.001.006.00030 (Box 6)
  - Perspectives in Clinical Medicine Addendum Syllabus, 2003, Second Year, UA146.001.006.00031 (Box 6)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Part I of III, 2003, UA146.001.006.00032 (Box 6)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Part III of III, 2003, Second Year, UA146.001.006.00033 (Box 6)
  - Psychopathology Syllabus, 2003, Second Year, UA146.001.006.00034 (Box 6)
  - Medical Physiology Syllabus Part II, 2001, UA146.001.007.00001 (Box 7)
  - Molecular Biology Syllabus, 1999, UA146.001.007.00002 (Box 7)
  - Musculoskeletal System Pathology Syllabus, 2003, Second Year, UA146.001.007.00003 (Box 7)
  - Nutrition and Medicine Syllabus, 2004, First Year, UA146.001.007.00004 (Box 7)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus, 1998, UA146.001.007.00005 (Box 7)
  - Addiction Medicine Syllabus, 1995, Second Year, UA146.001.007.00006 (Box 7)
  - Addiction Medicine Syllabus, 2003, Second Year, UA146.001.007.00007 (Box 7)
  - Biochemistry Conferences, 1999, First Year, UA146.001.007.00008 (Box 7)
  - Cell Tissue and Organ Biology Syllabus Part I, 1999, UA146.001.007.00009 (Box 7)
  - Class of 1998 Second Year Fall Semester, 1998, Second Year, UA146.001.007.00010 (Box 7)
  - Class of 1999 First Year Fall Semester, 1999, First Year, UA146.001.007.00011 (Box 7)
  - Interviewing and the Doctor Patient Relationship Syllabus, 2004, First Year, UA146.001.007.00012 (Box 7)
  - Introduction to Family Medicine Block, 1995, UA146.001.007.00013 (Box 7)
  - Introductory Block, 1995, UA146.001.007.00014 (Box 7)
  - Medical Microbiology Laboratory, 1998, UA146.001.007.00015 (Box 7)
  - Medical Physiology Syllabus Part I, 1999, UA146.001.007.00016 (Box 7)
  - Molecular Biology Syllabus, 2004, UA146.001.007.00017 (Box 7)
  - Musculoskeletal Pathophysiology Syllabus, 1998, Second Year, UA146.001.007.00018 (Box 7)
  - Musculoskeletal System Pathology Syllabus, 1998, Second Year, UA146.001.007.00019 (Box 7)
  - Neuroscience Lab Manuel, 1998, Second Year, UA146.001.007.00020 (Box 7)
  - Neuroscience Syllabus, 1998, Second Year, UA146.001.007.00021 (Box 7)
  - Nutrition and Medicine Syllabus, 1995, First Year, UA146.001.007.00022 (Box 7)
  - Nutrition and Medicine Syllabus, 2003, First Year, UA146.001.007.00023 (Box 7)
  - Pathophysiology Musculoskeletal and Infectious Disease Syllabus, 2003, Second Year, UA146.001.007.00024 (Box 7)
  - Patient Doctor Society Syllabus, 2004, First Year, UA146.001.007.00025 (Box 7)
  - Patient Doctor Society Syllabus, 2004, First Year, UA146.001.007.00026 (Box 7)
  - Patient Doctor Society Syllabus III of IV, 2004, First Year, UA146.001.007.00027 (Box 7)
  - Patient Doctor Society Syllabus IV of IV, 2004, First Year, UA146.001.007.00028 (Box 7)
  - Perspectives of Medicine Block, 1995, UA146.001.007.00029 (Box 7)
  - Pharmacology Syllabus Part II of III, 2003, Second Year, UA146.001.007.00030 (Box 7)